Name	NAGARAJ D
Designation	Mean Stack Developer
Email	nagaraj.info6@gmail.com
Contact No	9884353315

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE			
Brief Profile	 3.2 Years of Experience as a MEAN STACK developer – handling software product development using Angular JS, Angular 4, Node JS, MongoDB, Express JS, REST API, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript, ES6, TypeScript, AJAX, JSON, HTML5, CSS3. Have Strong knowledge in Angular JS, Node JS, Mongo DB and JavaScript Technologies. Hands on experience in developing web applications using Bootstrap Framework. Experience in using Gulp and NPM. Work collaboratively with team members to achieve common goals, while maintaining responsibilities and commitments. Possess good communication skill, attention to detail. 		
Employment History	SYZYGY Enterprise Solutions from April 2017 to till date. Teezle Telematics India Pvt Ltd. from Nov 2014 to Sep 2016.		
Total Experience	3.2 years		
Education	B. Tech from PSNA College of Engineering and Technology.		
Operating Systems	Ubuntu, Windows 7,10		
Languages/Technologies	Angular JS, Angular 4, Node JS, Mongo DB, Express JS, REST API, ES6,		
/ Framework	TypeScript, JavaScript, jQuery, Twitter Bootstrap, PhoneGap, AJAX, JSON, HTML5, CSS3		
Tools	WebStorm, Visual Studio		
Configuration	GitHub		
Management			
Version Control System	Bitbucket		

PROJECT EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
SYZYGY-CRM	AngularJS, Node JS, MongoDB, Express JS, ES6, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap,	Developer	March 2018 to June 2018	3

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYZYGY — CRM is including the following modules like user management, payment management and ticket management. Every user can see their current plan details and renewal their Plans by make payment for every month. User can raise a ticket to support or technical team based on their requirements, queries, feature request, complaint or new connection request.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Database design.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications

Technologies Used – Angular 4, Node Js, ES6, MongoDB, Express Js.

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
SYZYGY-IDEABUCKET	HTML5, CSS3, Angular4, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express JS	Developer	Dec 2017 to Feb 2018	2

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYZYGY – IDEABUCKET provides the latest technology information and innovative idea related concepts between the employee of an organization. It also acts as collaboration tool between the management and employee.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Database design.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications

Technologies Used – Angular 4, Node Js, ES6, MongoDB, Express Js.

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
SYZYGY-PARKING	HTML5, CSS3, Angular JS, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express JS	Developer	Aug 2017 to Nov 2017	3

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYZYGY – PARKING provides information about the available parking spaces to the users as location wise, area wise. Users can select the parking slots prior and make the payment and occupied Their desired slots.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Database design.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications

Technologies Used - Angular Js, Node Js, ES6, MongoDB, Express Js

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
SYZYGY-WALLET	HTML5, CSS3, Gulp, Angular JS, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express Js	Developer	April 2017 to Aug 2017	3

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYZYGY Enterprise Solutions is a fast-growing IT Services and Products Company, It helps its global customers succeed by creating modern and efficient solutions by creating modern and efficient solutions and by delivering those solutions, consistently, on time and within budget.

SYZYGY — WALLET make the Credit and Debit card payment easier and secured. This is implemented with the use of Complicated Algorithm

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Database design.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications

Technologies Used - Angular Js, Node Js, ES6, MongoDB.

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
SASH.CASH	HTML5, CSS3, Gulp, Angular JS, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB.	Developer	Nov 2016 to March 2017	4

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SASH.CASH is pocket Money App. A digital media platform to push advertisements as effective cost from the other medium. We resolve the pain of the advertiser by providing accuracy, reach and create an opportunity for the brand to post ad for massive reach efficiency.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Database design.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications

Technologies Used - Angular Js, Node Js, MongoDB

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
MEDSCOPE	HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB.	Developer	Feb 2016 to June 2017	4

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Medscope is a national provider of medical alert devices and services. Our products include land line and cellular units, fall detecting buttons and GPS based devices to locate patients when they are in the community. The monitoring of our services is handled by a team of dedicated professionals committed to providing the highest quality service 24-hours-per-day.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications.

Technologies Used – JavaScript, jQuery, Node Js, MongoDB, PhoneGap.

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
	HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB.	Developer	Feb 2016 to June 2017	

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MyCaref is a Watch phone the world's smallest GPS location device for Kids. When your child is wearing the Caref watch you will be able to see their location right on your mobile app and you will be able to call your child's watch and your child call you.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications.

Technologies Used – JavaScript, jQuery, Node Js, MongoDB, PhoneGap.

Project Name & Description	Technologies	Role	Period	Team Size
MYKIDSPORT	HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Node JS, Bootstrap, MongoDB.	Developer	Sep 2016 to Dec 2017	3

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MyKidsort GPS is a stylish and cool sports band that will allow you to locate your kids on your phone, iPod or computer. Kids love the style, parents love the safety.

Responsibilities:

- Executing project plans, project release plans and development plans.
- Core module development.
- Web service development to integrate with external applications.

Technologies Used – JavaScript, jQuery, Node Js, MongoDB, PhoneGap.

Educational Qualification

Degree	Institution / University	% of Marks	Year of Completion
SSLC	Board of Secondary Education	86.2	2004
HSC	Board of Intermediate Board	75.4	2006
Diploma	Dote	83.2	2009
B.Tech(IT)	Anna University	74.4	2014

.